(Howard:)Ooh, more details
about the new Star Trek film.
(Howard:)There's going to be a scene
depicting Spock's birth.
(Raj:)I'd be more interested in a scene
depicting Spock's conception.
(Sheldon:)Oh, please. For Vulcans, mating,
or, if you will, Pon farr...
(Sheldon:)- ...it's an extremely private matter.
- I'd like to know the details.
(Leonard:)His mother was human. His father
was Vulcan. They couldn't conceive.
(Howard:)Maybe they had to go to a clinic.
Can you imagine Spock's dad...
(Howard:)...with a copy of
Pointy Ears and Shapely Rears?
(Raj:)How come on Star Trek
everybody's private parts are the same?
(Raj:)No alien lady ever told Captain Kirk,
"Hey, get your thing out of my nose."
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Hi. Can you help me?
(Penny(entering):)I was writing an e-mail
and the A key got stuck.
Now it's just going, "Aaaah."
- What'd you spill on it?
- Nothing.
(Penny:)Diet Coke.
And yogurt.
And a little nail polish.
(Leonard:)I'll take a look at it.